Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Art and Art History, Records SC1101
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Posters, 1973-2014; Series 4
  - Art Practice and Gallery
    - What Did I Do Now? A Meander Through the Work of Nayland Blake with Himself, 2011-04-18 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      39189
    - Open Studios, 2011-03-11 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      39151
    - Fatima Tuggar, 2011-03-06 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      39146
    - Between A Rock, 2010-11-18 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      39038
    - Al Souza, 2010-11-11 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      39031
    - Wangechi Mutu, 2012-05-03 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Bruce McClure, 2012-04-24 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      39561
    - 1. Model 2. Release 3. Form, 2012-04-19 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      39556
    - Open Studios, 2012-03-16 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      39522
    - Instant Vintage: Artist Talk by Jeremiah Barber & Ellen Lake, 2012-03-08 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      39514
    - Artist Talk with Camille Utterback, 2012-02-16 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      39493
    - Open Studios, 2011-12-09 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      39424
    - Space Travelling, 2011-10-06 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      39360
    - Open Studios, 2013-06-06 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      39969
    - Brief History of Security, 2013-05-09 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      39941
    - The Etiology of Innocence, 2013-04-02 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      39904
    - Open Studios, 2013-03-14 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      39885
    - The Non-Fiction Imagination & the Shattered Screen, 2013-03-07 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      39878
    - Windshield Vipers and Language Barracudas, 2012-02-09 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Sound Installations (Inside and Out), 2012-11-15 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      39766
    - Motion Pictures: Artist Talk by Steve Rood, 2014-05-28 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      40325
    - Yoshua Okon, 2014-05-15 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      40312
    - Notes, Tales, and Insults, 2014-02-06 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      40214
    - Open Studios, 2013-12-06 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Seeing Secrecy, 2014-04-24 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      40291
    - The Body in Question, 2014-11-21 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      40502
    - Fushion of Art & Science, 2010-10-18-2010-11-12 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      10/18/10 - 11/12/10
    - Half Tilt Full Lean (MFA Thesis Exhibition), 2014-05-13-2014-06-15 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      5/13/14 - 6/15/14
    - The Materialists, 2014-03-11-2014-04-27 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      3/11/14 - 4/27/14
    - Cipher Screen: a film performance by Greg Pope, 2014-02-27 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      40235
    - Hi5 (first-year MFA exhibition), 2014-01-14-2014-02-23 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      1/14/14 - 2/23/14
    - The Rapture, 2013-10-08-2013-12-08 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      10/8/2013 - 12/8/2013
    - 2013 Stanford MFA Thesis Exhibition, 2013-05-15-2013-06-16 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      5/14/13 - 6/16/13
    - Public Discourse: Photographs by Robert Dawson, 2013-03-12-2013-04-21 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      3/12/13 - 4/21/13
    - Arsenal, 2013-01-08-2013-02-10 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      1/8/13 - 2/10/13
    - Sounding Board, 2012-10-09-2012-11-18 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      10/9/12 - 11/18/12
    - Notes from the Field, 2012-07-03-2012-08-08 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      7/3/12 - 8/8/12
    - Exit Strategy, 2012-06-07-2012-06-17 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      6/7/12 - 6/17/12
    - Never Odd or Even, 2012-05-15-2012-06-17 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      5/15/12 - 6/17/12
    - Breakfast is on the Universe, 2012-04-03-2012-04-15 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      4/3/12 - 4/15/12
    - Self Help Book Club, 2012-01-17-2012-02-26 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      1/17/12 - 2/26/12
    - Journey to the Edges of Color, 2011-10-11-2011-11-20 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      10/11/11 - 11/20/11
    - Holding Fire Waru! in Australia's Western Desert, 2011-06-28-2011-07-31 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      6/28/11 - 7/31/11
    - Bracket, 2011-06-02-2011-06-12 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      6/2/11 - 6/12/11
    - Scramble, 2011-05-10-2011-06-12 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      5/10/11 - 6/12/11
    - Off The Table, 2011-04-05-2011-04-17 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      4/5/11 - 4/17/11
    - Heretical Hierarchy, 2011-01-11-2011-02-20 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      1/11/11 - 2/20/11
    - The Art of Dislocation, 2010-09-28-2010-11-14 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      9/28/10 - 11/14/10
    - Excavating the Underground, 2010-07-06-2010-08-08 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      7/6/10 - 8/8/10
    - Square Root, 2010-05-11-2011-06-13 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      5/11/10 - 6/13/11
    - Design Unassigned, 2010-03-16-2010-04-25 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      3/16/10 - 4/25/10
    - Devil May-Care, 2010-01-12-2010-02-21 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      1/12/10 - 2/21/10
    - Account, 2009-07-14-2009-08-16 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      7/14/09 - 8/16/09
    - Wunderflater, 2009-05-12-2009-06-14 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      5/12/09 - 6/14/09
    - Deisgn in Balance, 2009-03-17-2009-04-26 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      3/17/09 - 4/26/09
    - Very Close to Far Away, 2009-01-13-2009-02-22 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      1/13/09 - 2/22/09
    - Every Push Pushes Back, 2004-11-19 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      38310
    - Ghostpile, 2008-11-04-2008-12-14 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      11/4/08 - 12/14/08
    - Expanding, 2008-09-16-2008-10-19 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      9/16/08 - 10/19/08
    - Gauri Gill: The Americans, 2008-07-08-2008-08-17 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      7/8/08 - 8/17/08
    - Senior_Exhibition, 2008-06-08-2008-06-18 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      6/8/2008 - 6/18/08
    - Transient, 2008-05-20-2008-06-15 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      5/20/08 - 6/15/08
    - Alternative Processes, 2008-05-15-2008-05-29 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      5/15/08 - 5/29/08
    - Design Unbound, 2008-03-18-2008-05-04 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      3/18/018 - 5/4/08
    - Age of Everything, 2008-01-15-2008-02-24 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      1/15/08 - 2/24/08
    - Sound and Video: a student show, 2007-12-04-2007-12-09 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      12/4/07 - 12/9/07
    - Leonard Cohen: Lines of Life, 2007-09-18-2007-11-18 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      9/18/07 - 11/18/07
    - Animals, 2007-07-10-2007-08-19 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      7/10/07 - 8/19/07
    - In Advance, 2007-05-29-2007-06-17 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      5/29/07 - 6/17/07
    - Lies, 2007-04-12-2007-05-06 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      4/12/07 - 5/6/07
    - The Landscape, 2007-02-20-2007-03-18 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      2/20/07 - 3/18/07
    - Sliding Scale: Gail Wight, 2006-11-07-2006-12-10 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      11/7/06 - 12/10/06
    - Studio Access: The Photographs of Leo Holub, 2006-09-26-2006-10-29 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      9/26/06 - 10/29/06
    - Modern Artifacts: Bay Area Abandoned Spaces, 2006-06-08-2006-06-18 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      6/8/06 - 6/18/06
    - 2006 MFA Thesis Exhibition, 2006-05-16-2006-06-18 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      5/16/06 - 6/18/06
    - Come Make Art: Steven Siegel, 2006-04-23-2006-04-30 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      4/23/06 - 4/30/06
    - Design Redefined, 2006-04-11-2006-04-30 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      4/11/06 - 4/30/06
    - Unbecoming, 2006-02-16-2006-03-04 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      2/16/06 - 3/4/06
    - Matt Kahn: A Commemorative Exhibition, 2006-01-10-2006-02-05 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      1/10/06 - 2/5/06
    - When the Hunters Gathers, 2005-11-15-2005-12-18 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      11/15/05 - 12/18/05
    - The Final Bow, 2001-04-28 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      37009
    - SLS Year-long lecture series overview: Kianga Ford, Alex Donis, Janet Cardiff, and George Bures Miller, 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - New Drawings, 2004-10-06-2004-10-30 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      10/6/04 - 10/30/04
    - Sabrina Raaf, 2000-03-31 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      36616
    - Perry Hoberman, 2000-03-03 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      36588
    - New Drawings, 2004-10-06-2004-10-30 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Chakaia Booker, 1999-11-05 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      36469
    - Elizabeth King, 1999-10-01 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      36434
    - Architecture as Landscape Lecture Series, 2001 Spring (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Spring 2001
    - Light in Architecture and Landscape, 2000 Spring (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Spring 2000
  - Publicity and Public Relations
    - AY 2011-2012 rack cards (Box 10, Folder 1)
      2011-2012
    - Commencement program, 2011-2012 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - AY 2010 - 2011 Rack Cards, 2011 Spring (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Spring 2011
    - AY 2010 - 2011 Rack Cards, 2011 Winter (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Winter 2011
    - AY 2010 - 2011 Rack Cards, 2010 Fall (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Fall 2010
    - Commencement program, 2010-2011 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      AY 10 - 11
    - AY 2009 - 2010 Rack Cards, 2010 Spring (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Spring 2010
    - AY 2009 - 2010 Rack Cards, 2010 Winter (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Winter 2010
    - AY 2009-2010 Rack Cards, 2009 Fall (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Fall 2009
    - AY 2008-2009 Rack Cards, 2009 Spring (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Spring 2009
    - AY 2008-2009 Rack Cards, 2009 Winter (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Winter 2009
    - Almanac, 2009-2010 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      2009-2010
    - AY 2008 - 2009 Rack Cards, 2008 Fall (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Fall 2008
    - Artstudi 151 Beginning Sculpture, 2006 Winter (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Newsletter, 1994 Winter (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Winter 1994
    - AY 199-1994 Rack Cards, 1994 Spring (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Spring 1994
    - AY 1992-1993 Rack Cards, 1993 Spring (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Spring 1993
    - Commencement program, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      1992-1993
    - Newsletter, 1992 Spring (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Spring 1992
    - MFA Show (5/18 - 6/18), undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
      undated
    - Senior Exhibition, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - MFA Show (5/21 - 6/18), undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Graduate Painting & Lithography, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Painting & Sculpture by the graduate students at Stanford (5/27 - 6/16), undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - CANTOR ARTS CENTER EXHIBTION: From Their Studios, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Open Your Eyes, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Faculty Photos, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 166 Deisgn in Motion, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 141/341 Invention of Modern Architecture, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 101 Archaic Greek Art, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 1 Introduction to the Visual Arts, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 191A/391A, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 181B/381B Seeing the Divine: Art & Architecture of South Asia, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 167/367, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 203 Greek Art in Context, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 185/385 Art in China's Modern Era, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ATHIST 102/302 Classical & 4th Century Greek Art, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 166/366 Aesthetics & Politics in East European Cinema, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 138 Sounds and Image, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - FILMSTUD 300B History of World Cinema II, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - FILMSTUD 10Q Comics - A Lively Art, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 234A The Harlem Renaissance, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 120/320 Art & Culture of Northern Europe, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 01 Introduction to the Visual Arts, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 229A Prepresenting Rality, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 121/321 18th Century Art in Europe, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARHIST 132/332 American Art & Culture: 1528 - 1860, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 107/307 Age of Cathedrals, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 507 Medieval Image Theory, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 145B/345B Modern Art & the City: Painting, Architecture & the European Avant Gardes 1910 - 1945, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 410 Aesthetics of the Icon, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 101/301 Archaic Greek Art, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 203 Greek Art - in and out of Context, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 292A Researching Africa: Problem & Theory in African Art, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 242A The City and Surrealism, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 106/306 Byzantine art and Architecture 300-1453 C.E., undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 143A/343A American Architecture, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 153A/353A American Art 1900 - 1945, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 232 Rethinking American Art, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 182/382 Arts of China 900-1500: Cultures in Competition, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 2 Asian Art and Culture, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 111A/311A Introduction to Italian Renaissance Art, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 186/386 Theme & Style in Japanese Art, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 195/395 Introduction to Black Atlantic Visual Traditions, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 105A/305A Islamic Art around the Mediterranean, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 104A/304A Art & Architecture of Ancient Egypt, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 003 Intro to the History of Architecture, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 113A/313A Sixteenth-Century Italian Art, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 206A Visualizing History in the Islamic World, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 516 Narrative Thory and Visual Form, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 169 Professional Design Explorations, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 204A/classart 110 Appropriations of Greek Art, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 174 Digital Art in Public Space, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 146 Painting II, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 170 Proects in Photography, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 70 Introduction to Photography, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 161 Catalysts for Design, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 60 Design 1: Fundamental Visual Language, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 167 Introduction to Animation, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 131 Studio Art 1, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 70 Introduction to Photography, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTHIST 185A/385A History of Photography, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 145 Painting 1, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 174A Rapid Conceptual Prototyping, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 138 Sound & Image, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 169 Professional Design Explorations, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 146 Painting II, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 152 Sculpture II, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 271 The View Camera: Its Uses & Techniques, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 184 Biology and Art, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 179 Digital Art 1, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 151 Sculpture 1, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 269 Advanced Photography Seminar, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 270 Advanced Photography Seminar, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 60 Design 1: Fundamental Visual Language, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 151 Sculpture 1, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 177A Video Art II, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 152 Sculpture II, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 276 The Photographic Book, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 270 Advanced Photography Seminar, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 70 Introduction to Photography, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 136 Future Media/Media Archaelogies, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 179A Digital Art II, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 176 Web Projects, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 170 Projects in Photography, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - ARTSTUDI 70 Introduction to Photography, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - FILMSTUD 152/353 Cinema-Machine, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - FILMSTUD 290 Senior Seminar: Movies and Methods, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - FILMSTUD 102 Theories of the Moving Image, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - FILMSTUD 4 Introduction to Film Study, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - FILMSTUD 230 Cinema Ideaology, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - FILMSTUD 100A/300A History of World Cinema I 1895 - 1929, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - FILMSTUD 100B History of World Cinema II: 1930 - 1959, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - FILMSTUD 111/311 The Body in American Genre Film, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Architecture and Landscape as Medium Lecture Series, 1997 Spring (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Lecture Series
    - Drawings 1960-90, 1990-07-03-1990-08-26 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Gallery Exhibition
    - The Art of Asia, 1990 Spring (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Visiting Artist Lectures
    - Jose Vermeersch Sculpture, 1989-10-17-1989-11-18 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Exhibtion offsite
    - Matt Kahn, Paintings, 1989-09-26-1989-11-26 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Recent Etchings and Aquatints, 1988-09-27-1988-11-27 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Wayne Thiebaud: Works on Paper, 1947-87, 1988-06-28-1988-08-14 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - MFA Exhibition, 1988-05-15-1988-06-14 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Romantic Themes in Art, 1988-01-12-1988-05-01 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Lectures in Art, 1988 Spring (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Lecture
    - Lectures in Art, 1988 Winter (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - MFA Exhibition, 1987-05-12-1987-06-14 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Lectures in Art, 1987 Winter (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Lectures in Art, 1986 Fall (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Sites and Related Works, 1957-1986, 1986-07-01-1986-08-17 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - MFA Exhibit, 1986-05-13-1986-06-15 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Prints 1950-84, 1985-10-01-1985-11-17 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - MFA Exhibition, 1985-05-14-1985-06-16 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Visions of Hope and Despair, 1985-03-19-1985-04-28 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Lectures in Art, 1985 Winter (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Lectures in Art, 1984 Fall (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Still Life, 1982-09-28-1983-01-02 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - MFA Show, 1982-05-09-1982-06-15 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Textile Sculpture, 1981-06-30-1981-08-16 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - MFA Exhibition, 1981-05-10-1981-06-14 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - The Founders & The Architects, 1976-03-14-1976-05-09 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Graduate Painting & Sculpture, 1975-05-15-1975-06-15 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Lectures in Art, 1973 Spring (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2017-010
  - DNF: Anderson, Harry W., undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Journal Entries, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Fund: Art History Graduate School Fund, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Funds: Bell, Mrs. Leslie Unitrust No. 1, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Brown, Peter Thomson, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - DNF: Bruner, Michael, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - DNF: Cafaro Family Fund, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - DNF: Cline, Dr. William, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - DNF: Cummings, Kaye B., undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cuthbertson, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - DNF: Eliason, Ms. Chatty C., undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - DNF: Dad, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Green, Dr. Jean Haber, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - DNF: Holt, M/M Benjamin, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Humphreys Alturas Foundation, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Kelly Mrs. Joan Stephens, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - DNF: Lopez, Mrs. Ramon (Nance), undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Lutkin, Eric, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Morrow, Frank, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Munger, Barry Alfred, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - McGhee, Katherine Drew, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - DNF: Nassutti, Nora, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - DNF: Putnam, Thorington C., undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Funds: Barbara Memorial Fund, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - DNF: Sayler, M/M Charles, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Funds: Slide Library Support, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - DNF: Rossi, M/M L. Jay, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Solomon, Elizabeth Hunter, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Funds: Speddy, Violet Lenore, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2017-066
  - Department Flag (Box 1)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2017-104
  - Photographs of students in studio and attending lectures. (Box 1)
  - Posters (Departmental events and exhibitions), 1960s-1970s (Box 2)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2017-244
  - Carol Terry letters (Box 1)